

PHD CANDIDATE

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

🗷 hgchi@purdue.edu | 🌴 engineering.purdue.edu/people/hyung.gun.chi.1 | 🖫 stnoah1 | 🛅 hyung-gun | 🎓 Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie in the fields of Computer Vision and Machine Learning. More specifically, I am interested in the Representation Learning for human action, 3D Computer Vision, and their applications in VR / AR devices and Autonomous Vehicles.

Education

Purdue UniversityWest Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Dec. 2023 (Expected)

• Thesis: Learning Representation for Understanding Human Action

• Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MS IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

· Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

Yonsei University Seoul, South Korea

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Feb 2017

Dec. 2022

• Advisor: Professor Soo-Hong Lee

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C7] H. Chi, K. Lee, N. Agarwal, K. Ramani, and C. Choi. AdamsFormer for Spatial Action Localization in the Future, *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C6] H. Chi, S. Chi, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition, Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023. Submitted.
- [C5] Y. Xu, A. Bazarjani, H. Chi, C. Choi, and Y. Fu. Uncovering the Missing Pattern: Unified Framework Towards Trajectory Imputation and Prediction, *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C4] H. Chi, S. Chi, S. Chan, and K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation, *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C3] H. Chi, M. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition, In proceedings of *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2022.
- [C2] H. Chi, S. Kim, X. Hu, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020.
- [C1] S. Kim, H. Chi, and K. Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020.

Journal Papers

- [J3] S. Kim, H. Chi and K. Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design (2021): 102932.
- [J2] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In *The Visual Computer* (2019): 1-15.
- [J1] H. T. Hwang, H. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)* 33, no. 3 (2019): 1333-1339.

Preprinted papers

• S. Kim, J. Bae, **H. Chi**, S. Hong, B.S. Koh, and K. Ramani. Egocentric View Hand Action Recognition by Leveraging Hand Surface and Hand Grasp Type. *arXiv preprint arXiv:2109.03783*, 2021.

Patents

RESEARCH INTERN

- [P2] K. Ramani, S. Kim, and H. Chi. Pixel-wise Hand Segmentation of Multi-modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. U.S. Patent Application No. 17/109,193.
- [P1] H. Chi. Computer Input Automation System. KR Patent No. 10-1745330, issued 2017.

Work Experience_

Honda Research Institute

San Jose, CA, USA

Jan. 2023 - Apr. 2023

• Conducted human pose prediction research for autonomous vehicles.

JANUARY 9, 2023 HYUNG-GUN CHI

Honda Research Institute San Jose, CA, USA

May. 2022 - Aug. 2022 RESEARCH INTERN

• Conducted research on future action forcasting task for autonomous vehicles.

• Developed a transformer-based alorithm for the task.

NEIL LAB Corporation Seoul, South Korea Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & CEO

• Founded and manage a start-up company as a CEO and senior software engineer.

- · Developed an office automation system specifically for automating office tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts.
- Designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically collects and integrate financial and personal data. (Relevant patent: [P1])

Skills

Research and Development Stacks Other Tools and Skills

Major Languages Python, C/C++ **Text Editors** Neovim & Vim

Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow, Keras Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab(Octave), R Web Frameworks Django, Flask, Node.js **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Computer Vision OpenCV, OpenGL IDE VSCode, Eclipse, IDEA Web Languages Nginx, React, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS Softwares SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB VCS Git

Academic Activities

Reviewer

• The IEEE Conference on Artificial Intelligence (CAI) 2023

- The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023
- · The British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC) 2020, 2021, 2022
- · Journal of Visual Communication and Image Representation (JVCI)
- · Journal of Computing and Information Science in Engineering (JCISE)

Invited Talks

Hongik University Seoul, South Korea

Dec. 2022 Guest Lecturer: Learning Representation for Human Action Recognition

References_

Karthik Ramani Professor, Purdue University ramani@purdue.edu **Soo-Hong Lee** Professor, Yonsei University shlee@yonsei.ac.kr